Time to work.
去干活吧
Sixty thousand a month for chopping trees down.
砍树的月收入是6万
The kidney I sold is worth 1.2 million.
上次卖掉的肾脏是120万
The right eye is worth 300,000.
右眼30万
And one testicle…
卖掉一边的蛋蛋…
How much did I get?
卖了多少钱啊？
Was it less than 100,000?
是不是不到10万？
So the remaining debt is…
剩余欠款是…
Thirty-eight million forty thousand yen.
3804万圆
Okay, Pochita.
波奇塔 我知道啦 赶快杀死它吧
I'll get paid about 300,000
杀掉一只恶魔
for every devil I kill.
大概能拿到30万
Be a Devil Hunter if you want to make big money.
还是当恶魔猎人最有赚头
This thing is a tomato devil.
这家伙是番茄的恶魔
Well done, Denji.
干得好 淀治
Its corpse can earn us a fortune in the black market.
这家伙的尸体能在黑市卖到好价钱
Your bounty is 400,000.
报酬是40万
That's 170,000, after paying your debt and interest.
其中扣掉债款跟利息剩17万
And after deducting the agency fee, service charge,
还有中介手续费、事务手续费
and management costs…
管理调整费等等杂费…
Only 70,000 left…
只剩下7万
And I have to pay the water bills
从7万抽一些付水费
and some other debts.
把其他欠债还一还
Unbelievable.
真是不可思议
Now there's only 1,800 yen left.
只剩下1800圆了
No food at home.
家里没东西可以吃
I'll have to survive this month with the money I have.
要靠这点钱撑过这个月
Pochita.
波奇塔
We only have a piece of toast for today.
今天的食物只有一片吐司
Why would you hire that brat to hunt devils?
干嘛雇用那种小鬼头当恶魔猎人？
He owes us a huge debt.
他欠我们一屁股债
To be exact, his dead dad did.
正确来说是他死掉的垃圾老爸欠的
Is someone feeding a devil really a good fit for the job?
饲养恶魔的家伙 有办法胜任恶魔猎人吗？
A licensed Devil Hunter
正规的恶魔猎人 才不会把恶魔的尸体留给我们流氓
And a good thing about Denji is that he won't fight back.
而且淀治的优点就是不会反抗
Hey, dog.
喂 臭狗
Eat this cigarette and I'll give you 100 yen.
你把这根烟吞了 我就给你100圆
Really?
真的假的？
I'm doing it then.
那我要吃了
I'll call you when there's another devil. If you dare run away, I'll kill you.
要是又有恶魔出现 我再叫你
Now we won't have to worry about food for the next three days.
这样就三天不愁吃了
I heard
我之前听人说
But a normal person's life is something we can only dream of.
对我们来说一般人的生活简直是美梦
I probably can never pay off all the debts.
这辈子八成还不清债务
And I most likely will never have a woman to date before I die.
我到死前都没机会跟女人交往吧
I can't ask them to come to this pigsty and I don't have money for dates.
没办法叫女人来这种烂房子
If my dream can come true,
如果能实现梦想 真想抱了女人再死
Kill yourself if you can't pay the debt for this month.
这个月的钱还没付 就给我上吊自杀
Brat, go beg, solicit, or whatever.
小鬼 随便你要乞讨或卖身都行
Just get me 700,000 before tomorrow.
明天之前准备好70万
Or you'll have to pay with your corpse.
不然我就把你的尸体大卸八块拿去卖
Chain… Chainsaw…
电锯…
It's a devil.
是恶魔
If you want to kill me, make it quick.
要杀我就快杀吧
I'm going to die anyway.
反正我就要没命了
You're hurt.
受伤了
Are you dying too?
你也快死了吗？
Bite me.
咬我吧
I heard that devils cure themselves by drinking blood.
听说恶魔喝血就能治好伤口
Bite me if you want to live.
不想死的话就咬我吧
But my blood is not for free.
我的血不是免费的 这是契约
I help you now,
我会救你
and you have to help me too.
所以你也要帮我
So I don't really want to die.
我果然也还是不想死
How about hiring me as a Devil Hunter?
要不要雇用我当恶魔猎人？
My empty stomach is keeping me awake.
肚子饿到睡不着
I think of the debts when I can't sleep, and that sobers me up even more.
睡不着就会想到欠钱的事 然后更睡不着
I've decided what dreams I want today.
我想好了今天睡着后想做什么梦
I'll eat lots of toast with jam along with Pochita.
我要和波奇塔一起吃涂了果酱的吐司
I'll flirt with a woman
跟女人打情骂俏
and play video games with her.
一起在房间里打电动
And she'll cuddle me to sleep.
被抱着入睡
Nice, isn't it?
不错吧？
My mom died coughing blood as a result of a heart disease.
我妈就是因为心脏患疾 吐血而死
Denji, there's a devil. Time to work.
淀治 出现恶魔了 上工了
At least let me dream.
至少让我做个梦吧
Can a devil appear in such a place?
恶魔居然出现在这种地方？
I don't see it.
我没看见啊
Is it hiding somewhere?
是不是躲在哪里？
Denji, we are grateful for your work.
淀治
You obeyed every order like a dog.
你像狗一样百依百顺
You did everything we asked for only a few nickels like a dog.
像狗一样拿廉价酬劳做牛做马
Right…
是喔
But a dog stinks and it disgusts me.
但是狗臭得要命 令我厌恶
We scamps also…
我们流氓也是
want to be stronger and make more money.
想变得更强 赚进大把钞票
So we decided to sign contracts with devils, just like you did.
便决定跟你一样 跟恶魔立下契约
We want the devil's power.
我们想要的是恶魔的力量
Devil Hunter.
恶魔猎人小弟
Seriously, these guys are so stupid and gullible.
说真的 这些家伙是笨蛋 笨死了
I said I'd give them the devil's power,
我说要给他们恶魔的力量
and they volunteered to be my slaves.
他们就主动变成了我的奴隶
Unfortunately, they became zombies because of that power.
可惜他们因为力量变成了僵尸
That's because I'm a zombie devil.
因为我是僵尸恶魔
Devil Hunters want to kill us. They are the worst.
恶魔猎人会杀死我们恶魔 最讨厌了
So I have to exterminate them.
所以要赶尽杀绝
Everyone, tear him into pieces and throw him into the garbage.
各位 把他五马分尸 扔进垃圾桶
Dammit.
可恶
The exit…
出口在…
Dammit. Let me go!
该死 放开我！
I never wanted to be rich.
我又不是想当大富豪
I just want to live a normal life.
只是想过一般人的生活
Is that too much to ask?
连这点愿望都没办法实现吗？
Pochita…
波奇塔
Pochita, time to work.
波奇塔 该干活了
I might get killed while fighting the devils.
我有可能会在跟恶魔交战时死掉
The only concern I have is Pochita.
我唯一放心不下的就是波奇塔
You might starve to death
你搞不好会饿死
or get killed by other Devil Hunters.
或是被其他的恶魔猎人杀掉
It's said that some devils can inhabit a human corpse.
听说有些恶魔能够占据人类的尸体
If you have that kind of power,
如果波奇塔有那种能力
I want to give you my body.
我想把身体给你
This way, you won't get chased around after I die.
埋葬后就不会被流氓追着跑
So you can leave this town.
你就能离开这个城镇
And then…
然后…
I hope you can live like a normal person,
我希望你能过普通的生活
and die like a normal person.
以普通的方式死去
Can you realize my dream for me?
你要帮我实现我的梦想喔
Pochita.
波奇塔
Did you successfully take my body?
你成功夺走我的身体了吗？
I like hearing Denji talking about his dreams.
我喜欢听淀治讲自己的梦
This is a contract.
这是契约
I give you my heart.
我的心脏给你
And in exchange…
作为交换 让我看看你的梦想吧
Pochita.
波奇塔！
The wounds are gone.
伤口愈合了
What the hell?
怎么搞的？
How can you still be alive after being cut into pieces?
把你碎尸万段了却还活着
Why? Disgusting.
为什么？好恶心
I hate Devil Hunters.
我果然讨厌恶魔猎人
Everyone, go eat him.
各位 把那家伙给吃了
These people were already living a rich life.
这些家伙生活条件已经够优渥了
Why did they still want more?
为什么还想过更好的生活？
But I'm just the same.
不过我也一样
I was happy with Pochita, but I wasn't satisfied.
有波奇塔就很幸福 却还不满足
I wanted a better life.
梦想要过更好的生活
Is that so? Everybody dreams.
是吗？原来大家都会做梦
Then it's not a bad thing.
那就不是什么坏事
It's not a bad thing…
虽然不是坏事…
but if you dare attempt to stop us,
但是敢妨碍我们的话…
you die!
就去死吧！
They devoured his body. Now he should be dead.
被啃食殆尽的话 总该死了吧
How did you…
你是怎样？
That little devil took your body?
刚才的杂碎恶魔夺走了你的身体吗？
Then we should be the same.
那我们就是同伴吧
That hurt.
痛死了
Don't come close.
不要过来这边
Get out of my way!
少碍事！
Don't come here…
别过来…
Don't come close!
别过来！
I told you not to come!
就叫你不要过来！
Die!
去死吧！
So you all
看来你们几个连心灵都变成恶魔了
Since I was hired as a Devil Hunter,
既然我是被雇用来当恶魔猎人
I should kill every last devil.
就该把恶魔杀个精光！
As long as I kill every one of you,
只要把你们通通杀死
there will be no more debt!
债务就能一笔勾销！
Someone did the job for us.
有人抢先一步了
There's one left.
还有活口
You have a strange smell.
你散发一种奇怪的味道
Neither human nor devil.
既非人类 亦非恶魔的味道
Did you do this?
这是你弄的吗？
L-Let me hug you…
让我抱你…
It's a human.
是人类
Maybe a devil took his body.
有没有可能被恶魔夺走了身体？
No, his face is enough to tell.
不可能 看脸就能判断是否被占据
We are Devil Hunters from the police. We are here to kill the zombie devil.
我是来猎杀僵尸恶魔的 公安的恶魔猎人
You have two options.
你有两个选择
Either to get killed by me as a devil,
以恶魔的身份被我杀死
or to get fed by me as a human.
或是以人类身份被我饲养
I'll feed you three times a day if the latter.
想被饲养的话 我会按时给你饲料的
Feed… Then what's for breakfast?
饲料…
Toast with butter and jam.
涂了奶油跟果酱的吐司
Salad, coffee… Maybe a dessert.
生菜沙拉、咖啡
What?
什么？
Isn't that just wonderful?
岂不是棒透了吗？